infinitynewtab.com 2019-01-15

# Privacy Policy 隐私政策

Thanks for your using. This privacy policy applies to all products and services offered by our company, including but not limited to browser expansions, Apps, websites, applets, etc.

Protecting user's privacy data is a great responsibility of us, this privacy policy is meant to help you understand what information we collect, why we collect it, how do we manage and use it.

If you are a resident of China, your relationship is with Chongqing Sentinel E-commerce Co.Limited.

If you reside outside of China, your relationship is with STARLAB.QLY TECHNOLOGY CO，LIMITED.

Chongqing Sentinel E-commerce Co.Limited is a subsidiary of STARLAB.QLY TECHNOLOGY CO，LIMITED in China.

* * *

感谢您的使用，本隐私协议适用于本公司提供的所有产品和服务，包括但不限于浏览器扩展、App、网站、小程序等。

保护用户的隐私数据是我们一项重大责任，本隐私协议旨在帮助您了解我们收集哪些信息，收集信息的原因，以及如何管理、使用您的信息。

如果您是中国居民，则您是与重庆哨兵电子商务有限公司签订本协议。

如果您居住于中国以外的地区，则您是与STARLAB.QLY TECHNOLOGY CO，LIMITED(星城科技有限公司)签订本协议。

注：重庆哨兵电子商务有限公司是STARLAB.QLY TECHNOLOGY CO，LIMITED位于中国境内的子公司。

## Why we collect data 我们为何会收集信息 

1.Help us constantly improve the quality of our existing products and services, in order to ensure that users are better able to use them.

2.We use the information we collect in existing databases to help us develop new ones.

3.We use information to help improve the safety and reliability of our products and services. This includes detecting, preventing, and responding to fraud, abuse, security risks, and technical issues that could harm our users, or the public.

4.Safeguard our legitimate interests. For example, we will collect and use your personal information for the purpose of advertising, sales and bonus.

* * *

1.帮助我们不断改进现有产品和服务的质量，保障用户能够更好地使用它们。

2.使用现有数据库中收集的信息来帮助我们开发新的产品和服务。

3.帮助提高服务的安全性和可靠性。这包括检测和预防可能会对您或公众造成伤害的欺诈，滥用，安全风险和技术问题。

4.维护我们的合法利益。比如出于宣传、销售和奖励的需要，我们会在法律允许的情况下收集并处理您的个人信息。

## Information we collect 我们收集的信息包括 

1.Customer support by third-party account.

The creation of an account is currently not supported in our products and services, so you need to log in through a third-party account (Facebook/Google/QQ, etc.)when you use our products and services.

In order to maintain our database updates and provide you with better experience, we might collect the information you provide and the content from the third-party account, we will manage and use it legitimately.

This includes: account and password, account information, login record, email address, IP address, and the other customer support by third-party account.

2.Your apps, browsers & devices.

We collect information about the apps, browsers, and devices you use to access our services and products, which helps us provide features like automatic product updates, optimization, etc.

This includes: browser type and settings, device type and settings, operating system, mobile network information, and products version number.

3.The activity data generated during the use of our products and services.

By collecting and analyzing the activity data, we could know the usage better, in order to make the corresponding improvement measures.

This includes: Custom settings, such as wallpapers, icons, etc. The textual content which is stored in local computer or the cloud, such as to-do list, notebook, etc. The interactive information during the use of our products and services, such as IP address, crash reports, system activity, the frequency of the use of websites and functions, your feedback and comments, etc.

Collecting the contens of this entry is just for product optimization, we will not disclose it to any others unless your agreement.

4.Web browser cookies

Your web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. we may use "cookies" to enhance User Experience.

These includes: session cookies, permanent cookies, third-party cookies, Flash cookies, etc.

They help our website remember your preferences and settings when you visit again in the future. Therefore, they could enhance User Experience. 

In order to make these cookies come into effect, they are stored on your device, and they won't be deleted when the browser is closed.

Or you can choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. 

* * *

1.第三方账号的用户支持。

我们提供的产品目前不支持创建账号，因此当您使用我们的产品及服务时只能通过第三方账号（Facebook/Google/QQ等）登录。

为保持我们的数据库更新并为您提供更好的体验，我们可能会根据适用法律收集您提供的信息以及来自第三方的内容，并在合法情况下进行管理和使用。

这包括：账号及密码；账号信息；登录记录；电子邮件；IP地址等其他第三方提供的用户支持。

2.您的应用程序、浏览器和设备。

我们会收集有关您用于访问我们的产品及服务的应用程序，浏览器和设备的信息，这有助于我们提供产品自动更新、增强优化等。

这包括：浏览器类型和设置；设备类型和设置；操作系统；移动网络信息；产品及服务的版本号。

3.您在使用我们的产品及服务过程中产生的活动数据。

通过收集分析您在使用我们的产品及服务过程中的产生活动数据，我们可以更好地了解用户使用情况，以便于做出相应的改善措施。

这包括：您对我们的产品所进行的自定义设置，比如壁纸、图标等；您储存在产品本地或云端的文本内容，比如待办事项、笔记等；您与我们产品服务的互动信息，比如IP地址、崩溃报告、系统活动、网站和功能的使用频率、您的反馈、您发布的评论等。

统计该条目内的用户操作数据仅为优化我们的产品和服务，除非经过您的同意，否则我们我们不会披露给任何第三方。

4.网络浏览器cookie

您的网络浏览器将cookie放在硬盘上以便记录，有时还可以跟踪有关它们的信息，我们可能会使用“cookies”来增强您的用户体验。

这包括：会话cookie；永久性cookie；第三方cookie；Flash Cookie等。

这有助于我们在您将来再次访问网站时记住您的偏好和设置。因此，它们可以增强您的用户体验。

要使这些cookie生效，它们将存储在您的设备上，并且在浏览器关闭时不会被删除。或者您也可以选择将网络浏览器设置为拒绝cookie，或在发送cookie时提醒您。

## The use of specific reasons 出于特定原因的用途 

We believe that it is reasonably necessary to use or disclosure the certain of your information in the following specific circumstances:

1.Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request.

2.Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.

3.Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues.

4.Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of us, our users, or the public as required or permitted by law.

5.We may share non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners — like publishers, advertisers, developers, or rights holders.

* * *

我们认为在以下特定情形下，对您的某些信息进行使用披露是合理必要的：

1.满足任何适用的法律、法规，法律程序或可执行的政府要求。

2.根据适用的服务条款，对潜在违规行为进行的调查。

3.检测、防止或以其他方式解决欺诈，安全或技术问题。

4.在法律要求或允许的范围内，防止损害本公司，以及本公司用户或公众的权利，财产或安全。

5.我们可能会与我们的合作伙伴（如发布商，广告客户，开发商或版权所有者）公开分享非个人身份信息。

## Search advertising revenue 搜索广告收入 

Some of the web search services we offered are provided by Trovi Search and its partners. For information on the web search services data collection, please visit http://info.trovi.com/Privacy, and the search provider's privacy policy (if applicable).

This agreement applies only to the Infinity New Tab, and other products of the company (such as Infinity(Pro), etc.) do not use Trovi Search's search service.

* * *

我们提供的一些网络搜索服务由Trovi Search提供，由Trovi搜索合作伙伴提供支持。有关网络搜索服务数据收集的信息，请访问http://info.trovi.com/Privacy ，和搜索提供商的隐私政策（如适用）。

本条协议仅适用于Infinity新标签页基础版，本公司其他产品（如Infinity Pro版等）均不使用Trovi Search的搜索服务。

## Security assertions 安全声明 

We shall take the relevant safety measures available at the moment to prevent the data of The Company from being lost, misused and altered. These safety measures include backing up data in other servers and encrypt the user's password. 

In spite of these safety measures, we will not guarantee the absolute safety of this information.

Our products and services contain links to other products and services, but we are not responsible for the privacy protection measures of other websites. We may increase business partners or share-brand products whenever necessary.

* * *

我们仅按现有技术提供相应的安全措施来使我们掌握的信息不丢失、不被滥用和变造。这些安全措施包括向其他服务器备份数据和对用户密码加密。

尽管有这些安全措施，但我们不保证这些信息的绝对安全。

由于我们的产品及服务中含有到其他网站的链接，但我们对其他网站的隐私保护措施不负任何责任，并可能在任何需要的时候增加商业伙伴或共用品牌的产品。

## Changes to this policy 本隐私协议的变更 

We can update this privacy agreement at any time. When we do this, we will modify the update date at the top of this page. We recommend that users check this page frequently to keep abreast of changes.

* * *

我们可随时更新本隐私协议。当我们这样做时，我们将修改本页顶部的更新日期。我们建议用户经常查看此页面以便及时了解更改情况。

## Your acceptance of these terms 您接受这些条款 

Once you use our products and services, it means that you accept this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please don't continue to use them.

* * *

使用我们的产品及服务即表示您接受本协议。如果您不同意本协议，请不要继续使用。

您若在本协议变更发布后继续使用，将被视为您接受这些变更，并且同意变更后的协议。

## Governing Laws and Dispute Resolution 法律适用与争议解决 

If you are a resident of China, the validity, interpretation, performance of this agreement and the dispute resolution shall be governed by laws and regulations of the People’s Republic of China, regulations of telecommunication administrative department and regulations of the computer industry.

If you are a resident of a non-Chinese region, the validity, interpretation, performance and resolution of this agreement apply to the law of your place of residence.

Any dispute related to this agreement or the performance thereof shall be solved by mutual and amiable negotiation. If no agreement is reached, the dispute shall be brought to the people’s court with jurisdiction of the place where the Company is located.

You and The Company shall together confirm that the option to sign this agreement is completely equal and fair to both parties. Either can choose to sign or not to sign this agreement without force. This agreement is a representation of ideas after careful consideration by both parties. There is no situation where one party increases other party’s responsibilities or escapes from its obligations. Any party who signs this agreement or promises to abide by this agreement shall be considered to have forsaken the right to question the fairness of this agreement.

* * *

如果您是中国居民，本协议的效力、解释、履行和争议的解决均适用中华人民共和国法律、法规、电信管理部门的规定和计算机行业的规范。

如果您是非中国地区的居民，则本协议的效力、解释、履行和争议的解决均适用于您居住地的法律。

同时我们将采取措施确保您的个人信息得到适当保护，并且只会在法律允许的情况下将您的个人信息转移到这些国家/地区。

因履行本协议或与本协议有关的一切争议，应通过友好协商方式解决。如果协商未成，则提交本公司住所地有管辖权的人民法院诉讼解决。

我们与您共同确认：本协议签署的选择权对于双方是完全对等而公允的，即任何一方可以不受强制地选择签署或不签署本协议。本协议是经过双方审慎考虑阐述的意思表示，不存在任何一方片面加大另一方责任或逃避应履行义务的情形。任何一方签署或承诺遵守本协议均视为放弃对于本协议公允性的质疑。

## Contact us 对本隐私协议有任何疑问，请随时与我们联系 

Address: 6/F, Tower A, Jinshan Commercial Center, 2 Saidi Road, Liangjiang New District, Chongqing.

Email address: infinitynewtab@gmail.com

Phone Number: +86 81219512  
+86 17132306281

QQ Group：194737859

Company: Chongqing Sentinel E-commerce Co.Limited/STARLAB.QLY TECHNOLOGY CO,LIMITED

Chongqing Sentinel E-commerce Co.Limited is a subsidiary of STARLAB.QLY TECHNOLOGY CO，LIMITED in China.

* * *

地址：重庆市两江新区赛迪路2号金山商业中心A座6楼

电子邮件：infinitynewtab@gmail.com

电话号码：+86 81219512  
+86 17132306281

QQ群：194737859

公司：重庆哨兵电子商务有限公司/STARLAB.QLY TECHNOLOGY CO,LIMITED

注：重庆哨兵电子商务有限公司是STARLAB.QLY TECHNOLOGY CO,LIMITED位于中国境内的子公司。

## Important Notice 重要说明 

Important notice: Any conflict occurred about the service terms and conditions between the Chinese and the English versions of the agreement, the Chinese version of the agreement shares larger portion of the legal effect.

* * *

如上述合同条款出现中英文表述歧义或内容歧义，均以中文条款为准。
